Guide to the Underhill Moore Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Family and Personal Papers, 1875-1948, Series V
  - Family Papers
    - Underhill, Abraham, estate, 1902-1906, 1920-1936 (Box 36, Folder 13 - 14)
  - Personal Papers
    - Columbia University student documentation, 1896-1910, n. d. (Box 36, Folder 15 - 16)
    - Columbia University Law School student notebooks
      - Code pleading, [1903] (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - Corporations, [1902] (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - Evidence, [1901] (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Jurisprudence, [1903] (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - Property I, [1901] (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Moore trust agreement and account-First Union National Bank and Trust Co., 1931-1936, n. d. (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Trip diary-Gibraltar, 1929 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence
      - 1902-1907, n. d. (Box 37, Folder 24 - 30)
      - 1908-1910, n. d. (Box 38, Folder 31 - 38)
      - 1911-1916, n. d. (Box 39, Folder 39 - 46)
      - 1916-1927 (Box 40, Folder 47 - 58)
      - 1928-1931, n. d. (Box 41, Folder 59 - 65)
      - 1931-Jane in London 1931-1932 (Box 42, Folder 66 - 68)
      - 1932-1934 (Box 42, Folder 69 - 72)
      - 1934-1935-Jane in Sweden, 1934-1935, n. d. (Box 43, Folder 73 - 74)
      - 1935-1940 (Box 43, Folder 75 - 80)
      - 1941-1942 (Box 44, Folder 81 - 82)
      - 1942-World War II correspondence with Kent Moore, 1942, n. d. (Box 44, Folder 83)
      - 1943 (Box 44, Folder 84)
      - 1943-World War II correspondence with Kent Moore, 1943, n. d. (Box 44, Folder 85)
      - 1944 (Box 44, Folder 86)
      - 1944-World War II correspondence with Kent Moore, 1944, n. d. (Box 44, Folder 87)
      - 1945 (Box 45, Folder 88)
      - 1945-World War II correspondence with Kent Moore, 1945, n. d. (Box 45, Folder 89)
      - 1946-1948 (Box 45, Folder 90 - 92)
      - Undated (Box 45, Folder 93)